Guide to the Records of The New York Institute for the Humanities RG.37.4
New York University Archives
- Series II. Seminars, Lectures, and Events, 1971-2016; 932.81 Megabytes
  - Springtime Wonder Cabinet, April 2011
    - Planning Materials (Box 93, Folder 8)
      Materials in box 93, folder 8 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Programs and Press (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Poster (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - State by State: A Panoramic Portrait of America Book and Film, September-November 2008 (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - "Survival of the Beautiful: Scientists and Artists Ponder the Aesthetics of Evolution", February 2012
    - Planning Materials (Box 93, Folder 14)
      Materials in box 93, folder 14 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Press and Program (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Poster (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - "Tarkovsky Interruptus", March 2012
    - Postcard and Press (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Poster (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Taste Seminar -- David Rieff and Edmund White, undated; cuid4956 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Television and Popular Culture -- Tod Gitlin, undated; cuid4959 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Television Styles: Towards a Typology of the Viewing Public, undated; cuid4957 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - "Tempest Tossed" -- Poster, October 2007 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Textuality -- Perry Meisel, undated; cuid4960 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Theater Criticism -- Tom Bishop, undated; cuid4961 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Lewis Thomas -- "Some New Agendas for Science", undated; cuid4962 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Translation Seminar, undated; cuid4963 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Travel Literature Seminar, 1985; cuid4964 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Urban Commercial Culture, undated; cuid4967 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Urban Culture Seminar, 1984-1985; cuid4965 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Urban Culture Seminar -- Budget, undated; cuid4966 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - "Us and Them and Beyond: The State of the Divide between Believers and Secularists" Conference, October 2004
    - Correspondence, Prospectus, and Postcards (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Poster (Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
  - Utopianism, 1990-1991; cuid4968 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - "Vermeer's Daughter?", May 2013
    - Planning Materials (Box 93, Folder 18)
      Materials in box 93, folder 18 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Press Release (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - Poster (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - "Vienna: Jews In and Out of the City of Music", May 2004 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Vladimir Voinovich -- "Conversation on Writing and Politics", undated; cuid4969 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - "War Music: Recent Stabs at the Epic", April 2007
    - Planning Materials (Box 92, Folder 12)
      Materials in box 92, folder 12 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Posters (Box 96, Folder 5, Box Shared University Archives 150, Folder 7)
  - "Was Athanasius Kircher Just about the Coolest Guy Ever, or What?" -- Poster, May 2002 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - "Was Eadweard Muybridge the Father of Us All?" -- Poster, circa March 2003 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - "Whalesong: Past and Future, New York and the World", April 2008
    - Planning Materials (Box 92, Folder 16)
      Materials in box 92, folder 16 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Poster (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - "What Exactly 'Is' Going on There in the Dark?" Symposium -- Poster, November 2005 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - "What the Hell Is Going on in Bahrain? And to What Extent Is the United States Implicated?", May 2013
    - Planning Materials (Box 93, Folder 17)
      Materials in box 93, folder 17 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Press and Flyers (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - Audio Recording, UA_RG_37_4_ER_3
  - "What's Up When Birds Sing", April 2005
    - Planning Materials (Box 92, Folder 6)
      Materials in box 92, folder 6 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Poster (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Edmund White -- "A Boy's Own Story" Book Party, undated; cuid4970 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Edmund White -- "Trios" Performance, undated; cuid4971 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - "The Winter of Our Discontent: Stepping Back, Taking Stock, and Gazing Forward in the Wake of Occupy Wall Street" -- Poster, February 2012 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Women Writing Women's Lives -- Ann Snitow, undated; cuid4972 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Women Writing Women's Lives -- Readings, undated; cuid4973 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Wonder Cabinet -- All Day and Halloween Events, February and October 2009
    - Planning Materials (Box 92, Folder 22)
      Materials in box 92, folder 22 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Press and Flyers (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Poster (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - The World of Goods (Mary Douglas) Colloquium, undated; cuid4974 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Writing and Censorship Conference, undated; cuid4975 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Writing and Censorship Conference - Correspondence, undated; cuid4976 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - "Writing Hell: Curzio Malaparte and Vasily Grossman", October 2009
    - Planning Materials (Box 93, Folder 2)
      Materials in box 93, folder 2 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Press (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Poster (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - "Writing in Light" Conference -- Correspondence, Press Release, and Program, 1997-1998 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Elizabeth Young-Bruehl Memorial -- Program and Invitation, April 2012 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Eugenia Zukerman/Anthony Newman Concert, undated; cuid4977 (Box 31, Folder 4, Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Recommendations A-F RESTRICTED, undated; cuid4979 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Recommendations G-M RESTRICTED, undated; cuid4980 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Recommendations N-R RESTRICTED, undated; cuid4981 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Recommendations S-W RESTRICTED, undated; cuid4982 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Recommendations G-M RESTRICTED, undated; cuid4983 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Series III. Audio and Video Recordings, 1974-2010
  This series consists of audiovisual recordings of events sponsored by the Institute ranging from 1974-2005. Some of the recordings were previously transcribed, and those transcriptions are contained in Series II.
  Arrangement
  Audio and video tapes are arranged chronologically. Tapes from later accessions are added to the end of the relevant subseries, and then arranged chronologically.
  - Subseries IIIA. Cassette Tapes, 1974-2005
    - Lecture on Notions and Perceptions of Community, 27-Sep-74; cuid3672; 1 audiocassettes 00:30:00; Audio quality is poor due to echoey acoustics of room and distance of recorder from speakers; Handwritten label on tape: Richard Sennett 9/27/74 PM; There is also a small handwritten sticker label: 74-001; Case is labeled 74-001; Insert is labeled "Sennett." (Box 32a, Audiocassette 1, Box Shared University Archives 108, Disc 19)
      Access copy
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 5:19.
      Physical/Technical notes
      Recorded on single side of Sony C-120 Plus 2 High Fidelity, "Low-Noise Auto-Sensor" Audio Cassette tape
      Part of the New York Institute for the Humanities lecture series; Lecture by noted professor of sociology, Richard Sennett, recorded September 27, 1974. Professor George Carson acts as moderator. Sennett discusses various notions of community and their development in our perceptions of them.
      Community development.; Sociology.; Sennett, Richard, 1943-; Carson, George
    - Richard Sennett, Wellfleet Conference, 21-Aug-76; cuid3673; 1 audiocassettes 96 minutes; Each side of the tape contains approximately 48 minutes of audio; Audio quality is good, recorder placed close to speakers; Cassette label: Richard Sennett. Wellfleet Conf. Parts #1 & #2. (typed) Side 4-Session 2 (handwritten); Case Label: 76-001; Insert label: Richard Sennett Wellfleet Conference, Saturday August 21, 1976 Part #1 (Side A) Part # 2 (Side B); Recording begins after lecture/discussion, giving no context or topic being discussed or even the name of the speaker. (Box 32a, Folder 2, Box Shared University Archives 108, Item 20, 21)
      Recorded on both sides of a Sony C-90, Low-Noise Compact Cassette. Serial number 402012.
      Discussions led by Richard Sennett at the 1976 Wellfleet Conference. Sennett does a lot of the talking but there are multiple participants discussing politics and religion.
      Access copy available on two CDs: ACCESS 5:20 (Side A) and ACCESS 5:21 (Side B).
    - Richard Sennett, "Broadband" ABC Radio, April 4, 1978; cuid3674; 1 audiocassettes 60 minutes; Each side of the tape contains approximately 30 minutes of audio; Cassette Label: Broadband 4/4/78; Case label: 78-001; Insert label: "Broadband" 4/4/78, ABC Radio 2 & 3, 7:15 PM, Richard Sennett program, Side 1 ends "but it seemed to work." Continued on Side 2, Duration 60" (Box 32a, Folder 3, Box Shared University Archives 108, Item 22)
      Appearing on ABC's "Broadband," Richard Sennett discusses his recent book The Fall of Public Man, which proposes that the growth of the idea of individualism and the western obsession with self-awareness and self development is the most reactionary force in public life.
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      Recorded on both sides of a Scotch C-60, Low Noise, High Density cassette (S-C-60). Tape may be approximately dated by the insert which has a coupon offer expiring December 31, 1973.
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 5:22.
    - Doing Justice With Bakke Tape 1, June 8, 1978; cuid3675; 1 audiocassettes; Handwritten Label: 6-8-78 Tape # I Doing Justice with "Bakke" June 8, 1978
      - Original Recording (Box 32a, Audiocassette 4)
      - Access Copies (Box Shared University Archives 107, Cd 2:41A, 2:41B)
    - Doing Justice With Bakke Tape 2, June 18, 1998; cuid3676; 1 audiocassettes
      - Original Recording (Box 32a, Audiocassette 5)
      - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 107, Cd 2:42)
    - Roland Barthes - Dialogue from Videotape, Tape 1, 7-Nov-78; cuid3677 (Box 32a, Folder 6, Box Shared University Archives 106, Item 46)
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 1:46
    - Roland Barthes - Dialogue from Videotape, Tape 2, 7-Nov-78; cuid3678 (Box 32a, Folder 7, Box Shared University Archives 106, Item 47)
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 1:47
    - Memory in Romantic Song Cycles, Parts I, II, & III, 27-Oct-78; RG37.4-JL-3/RG37.4-JL-4; 2 audiocassettes 75 minutes; Each side of the tape 1 contains approximately 30 minutes of audio. Side 1 of tape 2 contains approximately 17 minutes of audio; Tape label: JAMES LECTURE 10/27/78, Charles Rosen "Memory in Romantic Song Cycles"; Additional tape label: 78-006; Case label: RG 37.4-JL-3, Memory in Romantic Song Cycles - Charles Rossen (sic) 10/27/78 Part I/II, 78-006 (Box 32a, Folder 8, Box Shared University Archives 108, Item 23, Item 24)
      Access copy available on 2 CDs: ACCESS 5:23 & ACCESS 5:24.
      Famed American concert pianist opens the Fall 1978 James Lecture series with a discussion of Memory in Romantic Song Cycles; lecture is followed by 3 minutes of Q&A.
      Recorded on three sides of two Scotch Dynarange 60 cassettes.
      Romanticism -- England; Studies in the romantic age; Song cycles; Memory; Ramond, Louis-François, 1755-1827; New York Institute for the Humanities; Rosen, Charles, 1927-2012; Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827; Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828; Schumann, Robert, 1810-1856
    - V.S. Naipaul Tape 1, 4-Apr-79; RG37.4-JL-5 (Box 32a, Folder 10, Box Shared University Archives 106, Item 48)
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 1:48
    - V.S. Naipaul Tape 2, 4-Apr-79; RG37.4-JL-6 (Box 32a, Folder 11, Box Shared University Archives 106, Item 49)
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 1:49
    - Stephen Spender, October 24, 1980; RG37.4-JL-7
      - Original recording (Box 33, Audiocassette 1)
      - Access Copies (Box Shared University Archives 107, Cd 1, 2)
    - V.S. Naipaul and Richard Sennett, 11-Nov-80; RG37.4-JL-8 (Box 33, Folder 2, Box Shared University Archives 106, Item 50)
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 1:50
    - Michel Foucault and Richard Sennett, "Sexuality and Solitude", 31-Oct-80; RG37.4-JL-9 (Box 33, Folder 3, Box Shared University Archives 106, Item 51-52)
      Access copy available on 2 CDs: ACCESS 1:51 and ACCESS 1:52
    - Culture of Cities Seminar, 13-Feb-81; cuid3679 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Sean Wilenty, Comparative Cultural Studies, 20-Feb-81; cuid3680 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Maynard Solomon, Biography Seminar, 24-Feb-81; cuid3681 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Jurgen Habermas, After Postmodernity Lecture, 6-Mar-81; cuid3682 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Luisa Valenzuela, "On Writing and Politics", 11-Mar-81; cuid3683 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Aileen Ward, Biography Seminar "Keats and Identity" no. 6, 17-Mar-81; cuid3684 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Bernard Gifford, 20-Mar-81; cuid3685 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - McLaughlin, Fundamentalism Tape 1, 20-Mar-81; cuid3686 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Fundamentalism Tape 2, 21-Mar-81; cuid3687 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Fundamentalism Tape 3, 21-Mar-81; cuid3688 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Fundamentalism Tape 4, 21-Mar-81; cuid3689 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Susan Sontag, "On Communism" Session 1, 23-Mar-81; 2018; cuid659 (Box 34, Folder 1, Cassette cuid659, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records cuid659, Box Shared University Archives 119, Disk 1, Disk 2)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      1/8" audiocassette, 95 min.
    - Communism Session 2, 23-Mar-81; 2018; cuid660 (Box 34, Folder 2, Cassette cuid660, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records cuid660, Box Shared University Archives 119, Disk 3, Disk 4)
      1/8" audiocassette, 81 min.
      Preservation note: "Audio quality is fair to poor"
    - Bill Taylor, Culture of Cities, "Age of Innocence" Tape 1, 27-Mar-81; cuid3690 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Bill Taylor, Culture of Cities, "Age of Innocence" Tape 2, 27-Mar-81; cuid3691 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Aileen Ward on Blake, 27-Mar-81; cuid3692 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Communism Seminar - Neier, Sontag, Sennett, Reiff, Straus, White, Cohen, Padilla, March 30, 1981; cuid3693; 2 audiocassettes
      Sontag, Susan, 1933-2004; Neier, Aryeh, 1937-; Rieff, David; Sennett, Richard, 1943-
      - Original Recording (Box 34, Audiocassette 6)
      - Access Copies (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:13-11:14)
    - Fundamentalism Tape 5, 31-Mar-81; cuid3694 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Justin Kaplan Luncheon, 3-Apr-81; cuid3695 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Susan Sontag, "On Communism" Tape 1, 6-Apr-81; 2018; cuid661 (Box 34, Folder 9, Cassette cuid661, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records cuid661, Box Shared University Archives 119, Disk 5, Disk 6)
    - Susan Sontag, "On Communism" Tape 2, 6-Apr-81; 2018; cuid662 (Box 34, Folder 10, Cassette cuid662, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records cuid662, Box Shared University Archives 119, Disk 7)
      1/8" audiocassette, 4 min.
      Preservation note: "Side 2 is blank"
    - Susan Sontag, "On Communism" Tape 1, 13-Apr-81; 2018; cuid663 (Box 34, Folder 11, Cassette cuid663, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records cuid663, Box Shared University Archives 119, Disk 8, Disk 9)
    - Susan Sontag, "On Communism" Tape 2, 13-Apr-81; 2018; cuid664 (Box 34, Folder 12, Cassette cuid664, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records cuid664, Box Shared University Archives 119, Disk 10)
      1/8" audiocassette, 22 min.
      Preservation note: "Side 1: Audio level begins very low - volume boost given at different levels on the access copy; Side 2 is blank"
    - Anthony Vidler, Culture of Cities Tape 1, 17-Apr-81; cuid3696 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Anthony Vidler, Culture of Cities Tape 2, 17-Apr-81; cuid3697 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Ronald Dworkin, 17-Mar-81; cuid3698 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Communism and the Intellectual, 4-May-81; 2018; cuid665 (Box 35, Folder 2, Cassette cuid665, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records cuid665, Box Shared University Archives 119, Disk 11)
      1/8" audiocassette, 61 min.
      Preservation note: "Side 1: 00:00:00;xx - 00:12:37;xx and Side 2: 00:24:09;xx - 00:30:30;xx [end] - O-music content unrelated to the discussion being recorded (removed from the access copy)"
    - Susan Sontag (back from China), "On Communism" Tape 1, 4-May-81; 2018; cuid666 (Box 35, Folder 3, Cassette cuid666, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records cuid666, Box Shared University Archives 119, Disk 12, Disk 13)
    - Culture of Cities?, 8-May-81; cuid3699 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Patrizia Lombardo and Carl Schorske, Comaparative Cultural Studies Tape 1, 12-May-81; cuid3700 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Patrizia Lombardo and Carl Schorske, Comaparative Cultural Studies Tape 2, 12-May-81; cuid3701 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - John Mason, Faurisson, 13-May-81; cuid3702 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Todd Gitlin, Media and Popular Culture Tape 1, 29-Jul-81; cuid3703 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Todd Gitlin, Media and Popular Culture Tape 2, 29-Jul-81; cuid3704 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Todd Gitlin, Media and Popular Culture, 12-Aug-81; cuid3705 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Todd Gitlin, Media and Popular Culture, 19-Aug- 81; cuid3706 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Todd Gitlin, Media and Popular Culture, 26-Aug-81; cuid3707 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - E. Kendall on Tchaikovsky Festival, 2-Oct-81; cuid3708 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Todd Gitlin on Nuclear Proliferation, 8-Oct-81; cuid3709 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Fracois Furet on Tocqueville, 16-Oct-81; cuid3710 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Victor Navasky, "The Writers Congress", 23-Oct-81; cuid3711 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Professor Edel, Biography, 30-Oct-81; cuid3712 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Edmund White, Taste - Sei Shonagan, 11-Nov-81; cuid3713 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Philipe Roget on Common Sense, 6-Nov-81; cuid3714 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - E. Badinter, Fellows Lunch, 6-Nov-81; cuid3715 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Aryeh Neier on School Censorship, "Island Trees", 13-Nov-81; cuid3716 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Taste -- Richard Howard on Baudelaire Tape 1, 19-Nov-81; cuid3717 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Taste -- Richard Howard on Baudelaire Tape 2, 19-Nov-81; cuid3718 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - E. Holtzman on Kings City D.A., 20-Nov-81; cuid3719 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Thomas Bender and William Taylor - New York Symposium, 20-Nov-81; cuid3720 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Taste - Lord Berners, 2-Dec-81; cuid3721 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - New Right Tape 1, 5-Dec-81; cuid3722 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - New Right Tape 2, 5-Dec-81; cuid3723 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - New Right Tape 3, 5-Dec-81; cuid3724 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - New Right Tape 4, 5-Dec-81; cuid3725 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - New Right Tape 5, 5-Dec-81; cuid3726 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Architecture in New York Colloquium, 9-Dec-81; cuid3727 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Jarek Anders, Writing and Politics in Poland, 10-Dec-81; 2018; cuid667 (Box 37, Folder 8, Cassette cuid667, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records cuid667, Box Shared University Archives 119, Disk 14)
      1/8" audiocassette, 63 min.
    - Harry Levin, 11-Dec-81; cuid3728 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Ewa Kuryluk, 25-Mar-81; cuid3729 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Discussion on Polish Crisis, December 18, 1981; 2018; cuid668 (Box 37, Folder 11, Cassette cuid668, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records cuid668, Box Shared University Archives 119, Disk 15, Disk 16)
      1/8" audiocassette, 80 min.
    - Sipho Sepamla, Fellows Lunch, 8-Jan-82; cuid3730 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Censorship Seminar, 21 Jan 1982; cuid3731 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Beard Conference Tape 1, 22-Jan-82; cuid3732 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Beard Conference Tape 2, 22-Jan-82; cuid3733 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Beard Conference Tape 3, 22-Jan-82; cuid3734 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Beard Conference Tape 4, 22-Jan-82; cuid3735 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Richard Sennett, Democracy and Urban Form, 26-Feb-82; cuid3736 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Sex, Genders and Consumer Culture Tape 2, 28-Jan-82; cuid3737 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Allen Hunter on the New Right, 29-Jan-82; cuid3738 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Taste Seminar, Denis Altman Tape 1, 3-Mar-82; cuid3739 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Taste Seminar, Denis Altman Tape 1, 3-Mar-82; cuid3740 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Defert Symposium Tape 1, 11-Feb-82; cuid3741 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Defert Symposium Tape 2, 11-Feb-82; cuid3742 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Defert Lunch, 12-Feb-82; cuid3743 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Censorship Seminar, 25-Feb-82; cuid3744 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - John Leonard, Censorship Seminar, 11-Mar-82; cuid3745 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, New York and International Economics Tape 1, 12-Mar-82; cuid3746 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, New York and International Economics Tape 2, 12-Mar-82; cuid3747 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Linda Nochlin, Problems in Biography of Artists, 19-Mar-82; cuid3748 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - New Right Seminar 1, 20-Mar-82; cuid3749 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - New Right Seminar 2, 20-Mar-82; cuid3750 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - New Right Seminar 3, 20-Mar-82; cuid3751 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Monique Wittig, March 26, 1982; cuid3752 (Box 40, Audiocassette 7)
      Duration: 69 minutes; Preservation Note: Continuous static pops.
    - Tomas Venclova, Censorship Seminar, 1-Apr-82; cuid3753 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Edmund White, Trios, 19-Apr-82; cuid3754 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Bob Darnton, Censorship Seminar, 22-Apr-82; cuid3755 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Moshe Safdie Lecture, 25-Apr-82; cuid3756 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Censorship Seminar - Pornography, 13-May-82; cuid3757 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Women, War and Feminism, 14-May-82; cuid3758 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Ewa Kuryluk Luncheon, 28-May-82; cuid3759 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - H. Gans, Censorship Seminar "Self-Censorship", 4-Jun-82; cuid3760 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - "Independent Thought in Hungary" by Gyorgy Bence, July 12, 1982; cuid3761
      - Original Recording (Box 41, Audiocassette 5)
      - Access Copies (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:15-11:16)
    - Richard Howard, Pre-Modernism Session 1, 13-Sep-82; cuid3762 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Richard Howard, Pre-Modernism Session 2, 20-Sep-82; cuid3763 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Luisa Valenzuela, On Borges, 24-Sep-82; cuid3764 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - William Leach, Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture Tape 1, 24-Sep-82; cuid3765 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - William Leach, Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture Tape 2, 24-Sep-82; cuid3766 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - New Right Tape 2, 25-Sep-82; cuid3767 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Richard Howard, Pre-Modernism, 4-Oct-82; cuid3768 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, New York City Tape 1, 5-Oct-82; cuid3769 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, New York City Tape 2, 5-Oct-82; cuid3770 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Abel Decaux. Debussy - Chansons de Bilitis, 11-Oct-82; cuid3771 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Richard Howard, Pre-Modernism, 11-Oct-82; cuid3772 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Lawrence Pitkethly, Visual History, 14-Oct-83; cuid3773 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Nadine Gordimer, Fellows Lunch, 15-Oct-82; 2018-02; cuid471 (Box 42, Folder 13, Cassette cuid471, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records nyuarchives_rg37.4_cuid471, Box Shared University Archives 118, Cd rg37.4_cuid471)
      Original Format: 1/8" Audiocassette, Duration: 58 min.
    - Richard Howard, 18-Oct-82; cuid3774 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, New York City, 19-Oct-82; cuid3775 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Nicholas Wahl Tape 2, 22-Oct-82; cuid3776 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Richard Howard, Pre-Modernism, 25-Oct-82; cuid3777 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - T. Spires J.Coleman, Borges Seminar, 27-Oct-82; cuid3778 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Judith Wexler, 29-Oct-82; cuid3779 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Richard Howard, Pre-Modernism, 1-Nov-82; cuid3780 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - T. Nagel, The Mind-Body Problem, 5-Nov-82; cuid3781 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Charles Halpern, CUNY Queens School of Law, 12-Nov-82; cuid3782 (Box 43, Folder 8)